A Guide to the Records of the Office of the Dean of Virginia Tech Carilion School of Medicine, Cynda Ann Johnson, 2008-2018
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
Records of the Office of the Dean of Virginia Tech Carilion School of Medicine, Cynda Ann Johnson, 2008-2018
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
RG 46/1/1
24.2 Cubic Feet; 18 boxes
This collection contains office files from Cynda Ann Johnson, the founding dean of the Virginia Tech Carilion School of Medicine (VTCSOM). This collection includes office information, travel information, the School of Medicine's class information, reports and magazines, plaques, and personal papers, cards, and correspondence.
Johnson, Cynda Ann
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The collection is open for research, except the "Cynda - Board Review Flash Drive" is restricted.
Acquisition Information
The Records of the Office of the Dean of Virginia Tech Carilion School of Medicine, Cynda Ann Johnson, RG 46/1/1 was transferred to Special Collections and University Archives in 2019.
Biographical/Historical Note
Cynda Ann Johnson became the founding dean of the Virginia Tech Carilion School of Medicine (VTCSOM) in 2008. During her tenure, VTCSOM became the ninth accredited college at the university. All graduating classes earned 100% match rate to residency programs and exceeded the national mean score on Step 1 and Step 2 licensing exams. She also established the first Department of Interprofessionalism within U.S. medical schools. Johnson earned her bachelor's from Stanford University, master's in business administration from the University of Kansas, and M.D. from the University of California, Los Angeles. She was professor and head of the Department of Family Medicine, professor in the Department of Community and Behavioral Medicine, and director of the Family Care Center at the University Iowa. She then served as dean of the Brody School of Medicine and Sr. Associate Vice Chancellor for Clinical and Translational Research at East Carolina University, where she also led the development of the Center for Health Disparities Research.
Source:
Cynda Ann Johnson honored with emerita status, Virginia Tech News, April 22, 2019.
Scope and Content
The Records of the Office of the Dean of Virginia Tech Carilion School of Medicine, Cynda Ann Johnson contains office files from Cynda Ann Johnson, the founding dean of the Virginia Tech Carilion School of Medicine (VTCSOM). This collection includes four series, dating 2008 through 2018.
Series I: Subject Files contain office information, travel information, and the School of Medicine's class information. The series also contains a flash drive, which is currently restricted.
Series II: Publications includes some reports and magazines published by Carilion as well as by local magazines, foundations, or other medical schools.
Series III: Plaques includes an award to VTCSOM for program excellence for 2015-2016 and a proclamation from Carlion Clinic about International Clean Hands Week 2010.
Series IV: Personal Items includes Johnson's personal papers, cards, and correspondence.
Arrangement
This collection is organized by type into the following series:
Series I: Subject Files, which is arranged alphabetically
Series II: Publications
Series III: Plaques
Series IV: Personal Items
Index Terms
Subjects:
Medicine; University History; University Archives; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University; Virgniia Polytechnic Institute and State University. Virginia Tech Carilion. School of Medicine
Contents List
- Series I: Subject Files
  - Academic Affairs Committee of Virginia Tech Board of Visitors, 2008-03-31 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council Retreat (VT), 2009-09-03 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Tech Academic Council Retreat, The Hotel Roanoke and Conference Center, 2009-09-03 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council Meetings (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Accreditation (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Standards for Accreditation (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Accreditation Council for Graduate Medical Education (ACGME) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Admissions (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Admissions Dean (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Admissions Retreat, 2013-06-05 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Advanced Health Education Center (AHEC) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Alliance of Virginia and Nebraska (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alpha Epsilon Delta (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alpha Omega Alpha (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Reunion, DC, 2017-05-13 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American Academy of Family Physicians (AAFP) - Conflict of Interest (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - AAFP - Peer Reviews AI302RS (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - AAFP - Joint Grant Award Program (JGAP) Proposals, 2016-08 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - AAFP, 2016-09 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - AAFP Research Simulation Awards Program, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - AAFP, 2017-04 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - American Medical College Application Service (AMCAS) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - AHEC - Meeting (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Assessment (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Association of Academic Health Centers (AAHC) (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges (AAMC) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - AAMC Annual Meeting, 2009-11-06-2009-11-11 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - AAMC Council of Deans Spring Meeting, 2009-04-04-2009-04-07 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - AAMC Annual Meeting, 2010-11-05-2010-11-10 (Box 1, Folder 31-32)
  - AAMC Council of Deans (COD), 2010-04-10-2010-04-12 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - AAMC COD, 2011-04-02-2011-04-04 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - AAMC Annual Meeting, 2011-11-04-2011-11-09 (Box 1, Folder 35-36)
  - AAMC COD Board Meeting, DC, 2012-12-04 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - AAMC COD Spring Meeting, 2012-03-24 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - AAMC Meeting, Washington DC, 2013-01-23-2013-01-24 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - AAMC COD Business Meeting, 2013-04-06 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AAMC, Washington DC, 2013-06-09-2013-06-10 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AAMC COD Board Meeting, DC, 2013-09-18-2013-09-19 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - AAMC Meeting, Philadelphia, 2013-11-01-2013-11-05 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - AAMC Group on Student Affairs (GSA) Meeting, Chicago, 2014-11-06-2014-11-11 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - AAMC COD Admin. Board, DC, 2013-12-09 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - AAMC Meeting, New Orleans, 2014-03-28-2014-03-31 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - AAMC COD Admin. Board Mtg., DC, 2014-06-03-2014-06-04 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - AAMC COD Annual Meeting, Baltimore, 2015-11-06-2015-11-10 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - AAMC Learn, Serve, Lead; Seattle, WA, 2016-11-10-2016-11-14 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - AAMC Learn, Serve, Lead, 2017 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - AAMC COD Spring Meeting, 2017 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - AAMC COD Spring Meeting, New York, 2017-03-24-2017-03-27 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - AAMC Learn, Serve, Lead; Boston, MA, 2017-11-03-2017-11-07 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - AAMC Articles (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - AAMC COD Directory, 2015-03 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - AAMC COD Directory, 2015-10 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - AAMC COD Ignite Proposals (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - COD Ignite, 2018 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - COD Liaison to the GSA (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - COD Nominating Committee, 2017-03-02 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - COD Nomination (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - AAMC COD Roadmap Work Group (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - COD United States - International Medical Graduates (US-IMG) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - US-IMG (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - COD Work Group US-IMG (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - AAMC Council of Faculty and Academic Societies (CFAS) Meeting, Orlando,FL, 2017-03-08-2017-03-10 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - AAMC Data Book, "Medical Schools and Teaching Hospitals by the Numbers", 2010 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - AAMC - Financial Aid Summary Report, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - AAMC GSA Meeting, DC, 2014-07-08-2014-07-11 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - AAMC - GSA Steering Committee (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - AAMC - Matriculating Student Report, 2010-2015 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - AAMC - MCAT Exam, 2013-2015 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - AAMC - Medical Education Debt (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - AAMC Medical School Graduation Questionnaire, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - AAMC Medical School Year Two Questionnaire, 2017 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - AAMC - Medical Student Performance Evaluation (MSPE) Taskforce (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - AAMC MSPE, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - MSPE Taskforce @ 2:30, 2017-05-24 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - MSPE Taskforce Washington, DC, 2017-07-13-2017-07-14 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - AAMC - Member Engagement Review (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - AAMC New School Steering Committee, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - AAMC New Schools Consortium (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - AAMC New Schools Consortium, 2010-08-27 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - AAMC New Schools Meeting, 2011-05-05-2011-05-06 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - AAMC The Macy New Schools Consortium, 2011-10-17 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - AAMC - Online Designation Report (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Articles (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - AAMC Publications (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
  - AAMC Reports (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - AAMC Surveys (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - AAMC Webinar (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - AAMC Women in Medicine Contacts (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Anesthesiologist Assistant (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Audit - VTCSOM (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - BIC 2 Meetings (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - MS Biomedical Forensic Science (Donna Boyd) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Branch Campuses (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Brazil (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Breast Feeding Blackboard Materials (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Building Bridges Between Interprofessionalism and Practice, 2009-05-20-2009-05-22 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Campus Security (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Carilion Clinic (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Carilion - Audit (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Carilion Board of Governors, 2010-06-16 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Carilion Board Meeting, 2013-04-15 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Carilion Clinic Board of Directors Executive Committee, 2012-02-20 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Carilion Board of Governors, 2009-03-18 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Carilion Clinic Conflict of Interest (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Carilion - Family and Community Strategic Plan (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Carilion - 5 Minutes with Leadership (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Carilion Health System (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Carilion Leadership Conference, 2008-12-04-2008-12-05 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Carilion Clinic Leadership Conference, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Carilion Leadership Conference, 2017-12-12-2017-12-13 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Carilion Physician Leadership Retreat, 2009-07-17-2009-07-18 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Carilion Clinic Physicians (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Carilion Clinic Resident Orientation, 2010-06-16 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Carilion Spring Symposium, 2009-04-23 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Carilion Medical Center (CMC) Alumni Medical Staff, 2009-10-01 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Carilion - CMC Board Meetings (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - CMC Board of Directors (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Carilion - CMC Nominating and Governance Committee (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Carilion New River Valley Medical Center (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Carilion Magazine (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Carilion - Physician Magazine Editorial Advisory Panel (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Carilion Clinic Research Day, 2010-05-20 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Carilion - SMT Meetings (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Catalytic Health (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Charter Class Year 2 Orientation, 2011-07-12 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - SMT Retreat, Homestead, 2017-02-08-2017-02-09 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Center for Healthcare Delivery Science (CHDS) (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Center for Point-of-Care Ultrasound Research and Education (CURE) Proposal, 2010-05-10 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Circle of Excellence Conference, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Circle of Excellence, 2009-05-31-2009-06-02 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Clerkships - Years 3 and 4 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - School of Medicine - Clerkships (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Clery Act (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clery/Title IX - Johnson (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clinical Learning Environment Review (CLER) (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Clinical and Translational Science Awards (CTSA) (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - CTSA Grant (UVA) (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - CTSA Grant (UNC) (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - CTSA Grant (Wake Forest) (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - CTSA with University of Virginia (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - School of Medicine - Clinical Skills (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Student Clinician's Ceremony (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - CME/AAFP, 2015-06-01-2017-12-31 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Collaborating Across Borders (CABV) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Committee Elections, 2016 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Committee Elections, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Communications Department (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - School of Medicine - Communications (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Community Data (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Community Health (VT) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Competency Based Curriculum (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Complimentary and Alternative Medicine (CAM) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - School of Medicine - Conflict Resolution (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Cooking and Nutrition (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Cool, Jonathon M. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - School of Medicine - Costs (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Council on Education for Public Health (CEPH) Visit, 2008-07-24 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - CEPH (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - CEPH Meeting, 2011-10-06 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Culinary Health Program (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cultivation Dinners (Mark Morrison) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Cultivation Dinners - Dye Residence (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Cultivation Dinner, 2017-05-30 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Cultivation Presentation, 2017-05-31 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Cultivation, 2017-05-31 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - School of Medicine - Curriculum (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Curriculum Ideas (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - School of Medicine - Curriculum Management and Governance Structure (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Dean's Advisory Board (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Dean's Colloquium, 2014-04-28-2019-05-07 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Dean's Colloquium, 2015 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Dean's Colloquium, 2016 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Dean's Colloquium - Transition to Residency, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Dean's Council on Advancement (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Dean's Council on Advancement Presentation Notes, 2008-04 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Dean's Forum, 2014-03-27; 2016-09-01 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Dean's Manual (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Dean's Office Announcement (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Survey Link - Dean's Office State Compensation (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Delta Dental (DD) Presentation (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - DD Oral Health Lecture, 2013-01-09 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - DD Oral Health Lecture (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Delta Dental, 2016-06-06 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Delta Dental, 2017-01-04 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Delta Dental, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Delta Dental (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - DD Talking Points - Dean Johnson, 2018-01 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Dental Schools (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Dental Week, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Dept. Heads Council (VT) (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Dept. of Health and Human Services/CDC (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - DePauw, Karen (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Dermatology Residency Program (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Diversity in Medical Education (AAMC) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Deans Discussing Diversity (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Docs for Morgan (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Dean's Notes: Docs for Morgan (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Docs for Morgan Basketball, 2017-02-02 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Domain Day, 2012-12-14 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Spring - Domain Day (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Domain Day, 2013-05-31 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Domain Day, 2013-11-15 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Domain Day (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Domain Day - LGBT, 2014-11-21 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Domain Day - Rx Drug Abuse, 2015-05 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Domain Day - Other Materials, 2015-2016 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Dean's Domain Day, 2015-11-20 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Dean's Domain Day, 2015-12-04 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Dean's Domain Day, 2016-05-27 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Domain Day - LGBTQ, 2016-05-27 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Domain Day, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dean's Domain Day LGBTQ, 2017-06-02 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dean's Domain Day, 2017-12-01 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Domain Day, 2018 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Donors (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - School of Medicine - Dual Degrees (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - School of Medicine - Duty Hours (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - VTC Steering Committee Economic Development Committee (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - School of Medicine - Economic Impact (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Early ID Program Outreach (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Education Subcommittee of Senate Finance Committee, 2011-10-04 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Electives (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Employment Policy/Letters of Agreement, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Entrustable Professional Activities (EPAs), 2014 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Establishing a Vision for the Healthcare Workforce Pipeline in Virginia, 2009-08-24 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Affairs (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Assembly, 2015-02-26 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Development (Carilion) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Family Medicine Accelerated Track (F-Mat) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Family Medicine Clerkship Curriculum (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Department of Family Medicine (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - FAO (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Federally Qualified Health Center (FQHC) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - FFE Policy (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Financial (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Financial Aid (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Florianopolis, Brazil (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Florida State University College of Medicine (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Foreign Medical Schools (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Founding Donor Event, 2013-06-07 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Founding Donor Reception, 2014-05-09 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - France (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Georgesuared ABSC Program (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Ghana Visit, 2011-05-26-2011-06-01 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Dr. Carol Gilbert Event, 2017-04-11 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Dr. Jeff Gold Visit, 2017-08-07 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Dr. Jeff Gold Mtg., 2017-08-06-2017-08-07 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Dr. Jeff Gold Response (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Gottschalk Presentation, 2009-07-10 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - School of Medicine - Graduate Medical Education, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Graduate Medical Education, 2016-2017 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - GSA Steering Committee, 2013-2017 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - GSA Mtg. 12PM, 2017-01-26 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - GSA Steering Comm. 12PM, 2017-05-25 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - GSA Committee Meeting, DC, 2017-07-26-2017-07-27 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - GSA Committee Week Overview, 2018-07 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Graduation - Class of 2014 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Mike Grisham VBHRC (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - GWIMs (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Hampton University (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Hayes Seay Mattern and Mattern (HSMM) (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Healthcare Think Tank, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Healthcare Think Tank, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Health Sciences Technology (HST) Innovation District Meetings, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - HST Innovation District Meetings (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Health Sciences Library (Carilion) (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Health Workforce Advisory Committee (Virginia Department of Health) (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Henricopolis School of Medicine - Dr. Boaz (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Hokie Club - Roanoke VT Alumni (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Hokies and Health, 2017-06-03 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Hollins Leadership Team, 2012-2015 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Hollin's Play, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Hollin's Play, 2016 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Hollin's Play, 2017-05-01 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Hollin's Play, 2017 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Master Chief Hoots (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Humanism in Medicine Club (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Hutson, Susan M. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Pat Hyer (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - IAMSE Webinar, 2011-09 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - IAMSE Webinar, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - India (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - The Inn at Virginia Tech (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Integrated Clerkships (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Integration of Population Health in Medical School (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - IRS (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - International Forum (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - International Information (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - International (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - International Rotations (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - International Rotations Ghana (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - International Rotations Poland (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - School of Medicine - International Student Experiences (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Interprofessionalism (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Interprofessionalism Email (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Interview Process (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - VTC Institutional Self Study (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Jefferson College of Health Sciences, 2008-11-12 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Jefferson College of Health Sciences (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Jefferson College MSN Seminar Day, 2009-04-01 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Job Descriptions (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Keith's Case Wrap-Up, 2014-08-04 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Keith Johnson's Wrap-Up, 2015-07-31 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Keith Johnson's Wrap-Up, 2016-07-29 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Keith Johnson's Wrap-Up, 2017-07-28 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Keith Johnson's Wrap-Up, 2018-08-06 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Dr. Tim Johnson Scholar Series (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Joining Forces (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Joint Grants Awards Program (JGAP) (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Kazan State Medical University (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Kenya (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Collaboration in Kenya (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - King College (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Kissito Healthcare (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Korn/Ferry Institute (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - LGBT (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Liaison Committee on Medical Education (LCME) Rules of Procedure (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - LCME Visit, 2008-01-31 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - LCME: Medical Education Database for Preliminary Accreditation (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - LCME Visit Materials, 2008-01-31 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - LCME Visit, 2008-07-02 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - LCME Database (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - LCME Mock Site Survey, 2008-09-23-2008-09-24 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - LCME Site Survey, 2008-10-26-2008-10-29 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - LCME Institutional Self-Study Summary for Preliminary Accreditation (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - LCME Prep Retreat, 2009-01-09 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - LCME Mock Site Survey, 2009-02-04-2009-02-05 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Report of the Survey Preliminary Accreditation of VTCSOM for LCME (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - LCME Visit, 2009-06-02-2009-06-04 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Draft Report of LCME Survey to VTCSOM (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - LCME Site Visit, 2009-02-15-2009-02-18 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - VTCSOM Materials (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Team Report of the Survey of VTCSOM for the LCME (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Matt Joy Nomination for LCME, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Letter, 2014-01-21 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - LCME Report from Full Survey Visit, 2013-10-20-2013-10-23 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - New LCME Standards for Medical Education Program Accreditation, 2014-04-01 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - VTCSOM Status Report to the LCME, 2014-04-15 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - VTCSOM Status Report to the LCME Appendix, 2014-04-15 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - LCME (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - LCME, 2014-2016 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - LCME - Change of Ownership FINAL, 2016-11-15 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - LCME, 2016-2017 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - LCME Letter, 2017-02-24 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - LCME Change in Ownership Final Copy, 2016-11-09 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Consultation with LCME (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - LCME Visit, 2017-10-04 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - LCME, 2018-10 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - LCME Survey Mayo College of Medicine, 2011-05-01-2011-05-04 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - LCME Site Visit Drs. Barzansky and Hash, 2017-10-04 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Lead Virginia (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Learning Environment Advocacy (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Lease Agreements (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Legacy Society, 2016-09-03 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Liberty University School of Medicine (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Longitudinal Ambulatory Care Experience (LACE) Advisory Committee, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - LACE, 2016 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - M1 Community Welcome, 2016-10-29 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - M1 Community Welcome, 2017-10-11 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - MacKay SOM (Box 9, Folder 17)